<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Make Zurich Vol. II</title>
    <link>https://makezurich.ch/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Make Zurich Vol. II</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://makezurich.ch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://makezurich.ch/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://makezurich.ch/about/</guid>
      <description>Do I have to be a &amp;ldquo;hacker&amp;rdquo; to join? No! Everyone is welcome to join!
 Hacking is creative problem solving. It does not have to involve technology. It&amp;rsquo;s very beginner friendly.  But I&amp;rsquo;m really a complete beginner. Can I still come? Of course! Check out this great post by Oleg about getting started with hackathons.
The greater the diversity of backgrounds and skills, the more awesome the solutions will be!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Register</title>
      <link>https://makezurich.ch/register/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://makezurich.ch/register/</guid>
      <description>Ready to join for a great time working together on creative solutions to our city&amp;rsquo;s problems? Register today and be part of Make Zurich Vol. II!
First time at a hackathon? No worries! Everyone is welcome! Check out our FAQ
The registration is totally free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://makezurich.ch/guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://makezurich.ch/guidelines/</guid>
      <description>Team A team should consist of at least two and a maximum of eight people.
Code of Conduct Short and simple: Be excellent to each other!
License The following licensing conditions apply to works created at Make Zurich Vol. II:
 No transfer of rights: everyone retains the rights to anything they have created. Waiver: No one will exercise any rights of exclusivity with respect to information they bring in, even if otherwise could exercise such right of exclusivity under the law.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Press kit</title>
      <link>https://makezurich.ch/press-kit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://makezurich.ch/press-kit/</guid>
      <description>A collection of high res &amp;amp; vector resources for media usage.
 Dominant color: Züriblau, CMYK (Euroskala) 100C/44M/0Y/0K Font family: Comfortaa (Google Fonts)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archive 2017</title>
      <link>https://makezurich.ch/2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://makezurich.ch/2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Between January 27th and February 4th 2017, Zürich was the stage of the first community-organized hackathon around the topic of civic technologies, and in particular, The Things Network currently operated in the city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>